I'll dope you.
Have you so easily
forgotten that I bestowed
you with part of Emperor Crimson's power?
Now's your chance to
apply your unique talents.
You have eulogy and the
arms of Emperor Crimson.
Calm your senses and open your eyes.
I know you have what it takes to do this.
Now look at your immediate
surroundings and peer into the future.
I can't find it anymore.
I'm not sure.
I can't find it.
I can't find it anymore.
GameStop.
It's a dream that's a dream
that's a massive dream.
It's a dream that I'm dreaming!
I'll tell you,
can you
tell me?
I just say, I'm thinking.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
I'm thinking.
Break it and roll.
Whoa, whoa!
I'm going to go to the world.
I'm going to go to the sky.
When I'm going to die.
I'm going to die. Hell no!
I'm going to go and win.
Look carefully into the future
and predict that which shall be.
Ten seconds from now.
Birds!
The birds flew by just like I saw!
Boss, I think I found something.
It was hard for me, but Eulogy found him.
Ten seconds from now.
I can't believe it.
The guy's blending into the
cliffs to stay out of sight.
But I can't see him right now.
My bare eyes are useless as
long as he stays like this.
That's Risotto.
Somehow he's also able
to disguise himself.
Of course, he's normally invisible, but
you saw him because of your foresight.
Deep look a few seconds ahead
and see how he's going to attack.
There he is he's on the move.
What the hell!
I've got some bad news boss in ten seconds
scissors are gonna rip
their way out of my throat.
Peace, Deep.
Despite appearances,
that was not your death.
Risotto is the one defector
who's eluded the Family.
Dealing with him will result in injury.
You must use those seconds
of knowledge granted to you
by your foresight and deduce
how he will attack you.
Will do, boss.
He's definitely moving in for the kill,
so there's no way he's
using a long-range stand.
And so if my vision from
the future is showing
a pair of scissors being
lodged in my throat,
does that mean there's nothing I can
do to change my destiny, boss? Exactly.
You've seen the inevitable.
Now you must prepare for it.
There is no denying scissors
will sprout from your throat.
But see beyond that.
Discover the method behind his madness,
and his weakness is yours to exploit.
Once you do, move within two meters and
destroy him with Emperor Crimson's arm.
Damn it all!
There you are, die!
Rookie.
Then again,
in all my years as a hitman,
no one has ever been able to get
as close to yours truly as you.
Well done for a fledgling.
I'm curious, how did you know where I was?
Your abilities are so unusual.
Regardless, you must still die.
Ah, damn it.
How'd he manage to get them under my skin?
He hasn't so much as laid a finger
on me, and I'd never open my mouth.
I don't even remember catching
a glimpse of his stand.
But these scissors are
opening up on their own.
If I don't act fast, he'll cut
something vital in my throat.
I've got to get him out!
Those movements...
I was on track to bisect his trachea.
But from the way he put
his hands to his throat,
he's acting as if he anticipated
the scissors would be there.
He knows something.
Better be careful.
My next strike needs
to put an end to this.
Eat shit, Katsune!
Damn it.
How does he do it?
The boss is gonna lose his shit.
How the hell does this guy just disappear?
Regardless, he really got me good.
I'm getting wobbly.
Wait that's what's wrong, Deep?
Were you able to see Risotto's attack?
Sorry, boss. I'm here.
Did you see it or didn't you?
Your silence tells me you need to move.
Provoke him into giving chase
and pinpoint his location.
Don't fail me, you bastard! I'm scared!
I'm ready for what may come.
I swear he won't be
able to trick me again.
Keikatsu, I'll get in range
if it's the last thing I do.
Emperor Crimson has provided you
with yet another vision, hasn't it?
What did you see?
I'm asking you a question, Deep!
My foot, boss.
I know what he's gonna do next and
it's he's gonna go after my right foot.
And chop it off, no doubt about it.
I have to prepare to lose my foot.
What did you say, Deep?
He's coming.
I saw him out of the corner of my eye.
You have to get to safety now.
Wow.
You saw what the future holds,
so why aren't you moving?
Rysolto Niros.
A hitman.
All of his movements are calculated.
He knows how he'll kill me,
down to the last detail.
I can't even move my legs right
now, so running won't work.
Razors, now scissors.
He knew all of this would exhaust me.
He was planning for this moment.
Blast it.
Dopio's chance at victory is shot,
and it would take longer than
ten seconds to reveal myself.
Mysteria.
Losing a foot would be lethal
at this point in the fight.
Finding a way to minimize
the damage is our best bet.
Again, get the hell out of there!
He's going to slaughter you!
I mean no disrespect by saying this, boss.
But if I try escaping,
he'll kill me anyway.
I can barely move.
Staying put will help me
figure out how he attacks.
I've been consumed with thoughts
of him attacking me with
razor blades and those damn
scissors he stabbed me with.
However, I went about it the wrong way.
There you are!
His ability!
He uses the iron that's in people's bodies
and turns it into razor blades
that attack from the inside!
That would explain my exhaustion
and the frog bursting into blades!
I've got you figured out!
You use your stand ability
to suck the iron nutrients
out of living things so you
can make razor-sharp objects!
And since the blades shot
out of the frog first?
Instead of affecting us at the same time,
you are creeping toward
me from over there!
Damn that brick!
That vision from the future was spot on.
Someone did lose a foot.
Hey boss, I'm beginning to
get how this hitman operates.
We may actually come out
of this in one piece.
Boss?
Where did my phone go?
I just had it!
Did I drop it?
No, that's just a frog.
Oh, there it is!
Now, how the heck did it
get all the way down there?
It's underneath all these
rocks and covered in sand.
This is insane.
I've got to get to the phone
and report back to the boss.
Oh no, did it break?
Huh?
Thank goodness.
It's amazing how they can get these
phones so small yet so sturdy.
It's me.
You would be proud, boss.
The bastard's as good as dead.
Damn you.
Well done, Doppio Mio.
Bravissimo.
Should I be the one to
put an end to this guy?
Or would it be better to
wait for you to arrive, boss?
The death of Rizotomiro must be swift.
I'll snuff out the swine myself,
but you must be within two
meters for us to succeed.
I shall join you then.
Your job in the meantime is to get closer.
Right!
You can count on me, sir!
Huh?
There's something inside the leg
wound, and they're squirming.
Risotto's stand must live
inside of him. I see.
You have the power to divine the unknown.
You know what will be and
read my movements accordingly.
There's no other way you could have
known how I'd attack or from where.
Earlier, I surmised you were
nothing more than a helpless coward.
But now, it's like you're
a different person.
You stand here before me undaunted
with self-assured ferocity.
Your face is different too.
Those aren't the eyes of a boy.
No, it's like there are two of you.
Could that be what's going on here?
Absurd.
But now there's no doubt.
I'm closer than I originally thought.
Closer to the very person I've
been trying to track down.
Two years.
It's been two years since
you turned us into a
bunch of frightened mutts
waiting to be put down.
Now I see.
Whatever the hell you are, it's far
more than our group bargained for.
I'm sure of it.
What I want to know is who you really are.
I need to know your true persona,
and I'll do whatever I have to
do to uncover your identity.
Solido Naso.
One of the boss's aliases, huh?
Well, yeah.
Why the hell else would he try
hiding his daughter so quickly?
So we dragged our asses all
the way out here for nothing?
Damn it!
But if we can get our
hands on his daughter,
we might be able to find
out who the boss really is.
Tell him, bro!
Ever since the thing
with Sorbet and Gelato,
we've been stuck here like rats in a hole.
Wonder who's even guarding his daughter.
Since Pericolo isn't a
stand user, maybe Polpo.
Then, let's go.
Let's head over to Napoli
and ask him ourselves.
Hold your horses.
We should think through all our
options before taking action.
I'm as angry as you are, but
forget about sorbet and gelato,
and you'll meet the same end.
Failure means certain death, so take heed.
My blood's boiling.
But I'll deal.
Because he who cannot control
his emotions dies first.
He reattached the foot I cut off!
Yeah, I was right about you, Risotto Nero.
I know all about your
standability and its magnetism.
That's how you're able to control
your stand from a distance.
Tell me I'm wrong!
You manipulated the iron
inside my body so that I'd
hack it all up in the form
of those razor blades.
And you make yourself disappear by
drawing magnetized iron dust to your body.
Then you use it like camouflage
to blend into the environment!
How very astute. Fine.
You may have figured out
how my metallic operates,
but it really makes no difference.
You're far too late.
The damage has already been done.
Iron.
A fantastic element that
exists the world over.
Not only is it prevalent in sand, but
it's also in mineral water and plants.
Oh, and the healthy human body
contains traces of iron as well.
What are you doing?
You knew how he was going to attack you.
YOU CANNOT LET HIM HURT
YOU ANYMORE, UNDERSTAND?!
Boss, this is...
You deciphered my abilities
and managed to sever my foot.
However, the damage has already been done.
Nothing you do will change
that immutable fact.
Amounts of iron can be
found in great quantities
in plants like spinach
and organs like the liver.
And it's also a critical
component of the bloodstream.
What do you think happens when the
body is suddenly stripped of its iron?
In short, your blood turns yellow,
followed by you meeting your maker.
The iron in your blood binds with
the oxygen your body acquires through
breathing and carries it to all those
nooks and crannies inside your body.
Without it, however,
that life-giving oxygen can never reach
places like your fingertips and brain.
To put it another way,
now that you're nutritiously
bankrupt of iron,
your body won't circulate oxygen no
matter how hard you huff and puff.
You'll turn into a living
corpse before dying outright.
Alright then, now that he's on
death's door, what shall I do?
I could just wait until you die naturally.
Conversely, since I'm a little
short on time at the moment,
perhaps I should end this now.
Boss!
It's them!
They're near the mansion!
It's Pujerati!
He finally showed himself!
And he's not alone.
Narancia and Abakio are with him. What?
Damn it, Abakio's there!
We're out of time.
Deep, your next strike
must be the killing blow!
Use your power to see
Risotto's next attack!
I'm already looking, sir.
Risotto's gonna ambush
me from my right side.
After that, he...
he disappears!
I can't see him anymore!
It can't be.
What do you see, Deep?
Hurry, spit it out!
That bastard won't know what hit him.
He's gonna suffer.
Leave everything to me, boss.
I have a plan.
Right before my vision becomes reality,
I'll knock that smug head off
his shoulders and crush it!
Just like when I sliced
off his nasty-ass butt!
All right.
You must stay still, Dobio!
Any act you make now will be in vain.
Listen to me.
Your life depends on it.
Conserve your strength.
I'm traveling to your
location at this very moment.
In just a few seconds, I'll arrive to
dispose of Risotto. Few seconds? No!
I don't have that kind of time!
He'll be on top of me before I know it!
Deal with it!
Once I arrive, I'll use
my time-removal powers.
That'll undo the horrid future
you saw in your foresight.
But what if he offs me before then?
I have to kill him! Deep!
This is the only way!
If you want to live,
you'll follow my orders!
Your body has reached its limit.
I will not allow you to
sabotage yourself in my name!
Do you not understand
the position you're in?
Risotto Nero will not let
you find him a second time!
But if I can find him, boss, what then?
What if I said I had a way
to pinpoint his location?
You see,
I now know that the bastard's gonna attack
me by pulling the iron out of my body.
Here it is! His attack!
If his stand is strong enough,
if it has enough power to pull
the iron directly from my body?
then the scalpel will show
me the source of that force!
Gotcha now, Risoto!
You're so painfully predictable.
You knew magnetic fields attract iron.
and thought if you detected the origin
of the field, you could track me down.
That was foolish, as the reality is.
What you detected was the magnetic field
given off by my stand
in the foot you severed.
You didn't notice, but I left it there.
I did a lot of soul searching after
I was separated from my foot and
knew I had to make the best of this
situation if I were to survive.
Your body is essentially
devoid of oxygen at this point.
As I mentioned, the damage
has already been done.
You shouldn't even be able to twitch.
You're different now.
No more timid insecurity.
Then there's the change
in your physique and
your peculiar habit of
talking to yourself.
It's all making sense.
At long last, I've figured
out your true identity!
16th century German philosophers
knew the phenomena well.
So we're clear it's called
multiple personality disorder.
In addition to one's mental state,
sometimes one will exhibit changes,
like an increase in strength
or change in language.
To think I was foolish
enough to believe you were
nothing more than the
boss's most trusted agent.
But you're more than that.
You're extraordinary.
I can't wait for it.
When death takes you away, what kind
of contorted grimace will you show?
There's nothing you can do.
I'm far enough back, and
you've no power to resist.
Any hope you had is gone.
I've won.
This is the end for you.
Send him to oblivion, Metallic!
What? How?
Risotto.
I made sure that Doppio was aware.
I told the boy that he no longer
stood any chance against you.
Don't tell me.
I knew it.
The enemy already beat us here.
Luckily, they're full of lead now.
So much for their ambush.
How dare you?
Now that you've effectively
robbed my blood of iron,
it's not transporting oxygen
to my organs like it should.
Suffice it to say,
your power has made it seem as if
my body isn't actually breathing.
Which means the only thing Lil'
Bomber is currently tracking.
So how many do the enemy number, Narancia?
I've got one.
There's only one person
breathing on that cliff.
Is your stinking breath, Risotto?
How interesting what Doppio witnessed
with his foresight actually came true.
I was winning.
Victory was within my reach.
But you had to throw the scalpels, boss.
They were accusing.
Not always with a knowing.
What is just fiction?
Or what is the truth?
They have a mission.
They are the passion.
But they dare to tell us.
What's bad and what's good?
Stand up.
Join us.
Come on.
We'll see this.
We are the power.
Who's in the future?
Cause we are the fighters.
Just fighting for a ride.
Thank
you.